Super Cyclone is a action, science fiction film directed by Liz Adams.
When a super cyclone threatens the entire American eastern seaboard, a lone
meteorologist and a petroleum engineer must battle the elements to stop the threat.
Travis Verdon, played by Nicholas Turturro.
Sgt. Maj. Ramona Peters, played by AnnaMaria Demara.
Dr. Percy Cavanaugh, played by Andy Clemence.
Engineer Alex Rowell, played by Jonathan Le Billon.
Secretary West, played by Jamie Burton-Oare.
Sgt. Binning, played by Gerald Webb.
The term super cyclone (or supercyclone) may refer to:
1999 Odisha cyclone, a strong tropical storm
Cyclone Amphan, a strong tropical storm that affected mainly West Bengal in May
St-Just Super-Cyclone, a Canadian homebuilt aircraft design
Any large tropical cyclone
Super Cyclone, a 2012 film from The Asylum studio written and directed by Liz Adams
The film explores themes of tornado, hurricane,
cell phone, oil platform, tidal wave.
The tone is thought_provoking.